binomo.com 2015-03-28

# Binomo

Our company’s top priority is the secrecy protection and providing security of storage of all financial and personal information of its own customers and visitors. The rules given below (hereinafter - the "rules") describe how BINOMO LIMITED Anguilla (hereinafter - the "Company") collects, uses, stores and protects the personal information of customers. When opening an account in our company, using binomo.com (hereinafter - the "Web Site"), you, as a customer, are giving your consent to the collection and use of personal information a company described in these rules form.

## Personal information collection

Brokerage company collects all the necessary information at the moment the client opens a real or a demo account using a web site for transferring and storing under the protection of customer funds and assets, and for providing necessary services to the client of the company. All personal data collected by the company include:

  1. The data required for communication with the client (name, e-mail address, registration address, phone number, date of birth, and other information collected during the registration process);
  2. The data necessary to confirm the identity of the client (passport information, ID cards, driver's license). The client takes personal responsibility to provide correct, accurate and updated information about himself, as well as the obligation not to use this data to other people or entities. If there have been changes in the data, which confirm the identity of the client, the company must be informed about it immediately;
  3. The data on activity and action on the warranty of the client's account;
  4. indirect data, which include «IP» (Internet Protocol address of the client), browser type, ISP (internet service provider), transaction history and timestamps.

The company may collect other types of information, which is recorded at the servers of the website. It includes language, browser type, the last time the client visited company’s website and is done in order to learn the specific patterns and to block the access to the website for some individuals. 

## Using personal information

Binomo uses the client’s data for the following reasons:

  1. in order to confirm the identity of the client;
  2. for the purpose of processing non trading and trading executions;
  3. to ensure the fulfillment of the rules to combat money and assets laundering;
  4. to inform the client about the services and products of the company, which may be of interest to the client;
  5. to provide other services related to the relationship between the company and the client;
  6. in order to store the database on the trading account of the client;
  7. to execute the statistical analysis to provide the client with the appropriate services and products.

## Сookie-file

The Binomo Company collects the information not related to the information identifying the client personality, the one that becomes available as a result of the Company’s website usage.

The company uses «Сookie-files» in order to provide the operation of the specific functions of the website. Cookie-file is a test file that is placed at the clients computer at the moment he visits the company’s website, it allows to enter the website without the repeated entering the information and allows the company to identify the client when he returns to the website

Cookie-files used by the company do not contain any sensitive information or personal data. However, deletion of cookie-files results in the access to some functions of the website being lost.

## Personal data protection

All of the data provided by the client shall be considered confidential and may only be distributed within the company and will not be disclosed to a third party without a legitimate reason.

Client data can be used:

  * for processing by any employee of the company, in cases when there is a need to know such information to perform certain types of work,;
  * third party providing services on behalf of or for the company (associated with operations of the site);
  * auditors and their advisers, conducting audit of the company's business;
  * potential buyers and investors.

The company is committed to protecting the information of third parties that will be available to the personal data of clients, in accordance with established rules. The Company does not distribute information of its clients to such third parties, which are unable to ensure information protection. 

## Security

The company, in order to ensure the security of all personal data of its clients has implemented rules and technical measures to protect the information. All transactions on the company's website are safe. The company uses the server certificate that guarantees the company's license and Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) - encryption of data transferred. These clients debit cards are not stored.

## Passwords

The Login name and the password used by the Client to access the website are considered to be his private property.

Имя пользователя, а также пароль, которыми пользуется клиент для входа на сайт, считаются его личной собственностью. The Company is not responsible for the use of such data, nor does it monitor the client how to manage your account using such data.

In turn, the customer is obliged to immediately inform customer support about any unauthorized or suspicious activities that involve the use of his personal account.

## Link to other websites and services

The website of the company can not have the links to the other websites, which are not controlled by the company. Broker does not hold any responsibility for the websites, at which the links to his resource can be published without confirming the cooperation with the company’s website.

## Under-age safety

Company’s website is a resource open to the public and has no intention to be a destination for children. If the company becomes known that a minor has filed or attempted to submit personal information to register as a Client, the company can take steps to remove such information from the internal records of the server.

## Changes in rules

Broker may modify or update these rules. The information on such changes will be posted on the company’s website.
